Guide to the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME), District Council 37 Records WAG.265
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Series VIII: Ken Nash Collection - Audio Cassettes, 1986-1999; 310566
  - Subseries VIII:A: "It's Your City, It's Our Job" Audio Cassettes, 1986-1998., 310639
    - Unidentified Program, Jan 27, 1995; cuid6012; 310719 (Box 67, Cassette 132)
    - Black History Month, Mar 3, 1995; cuid6013; 310720 (Box 67, Cassette 133)
    - Retiree's Association, May 1995; cuid6014; 310721 (Box 67, Cassette 134)
    - Community and Labor Coalitions, Jun 23, 1995; cuid6015; 310722 (Box 67, Cassette 135)
    - Hispanic Heritage, Oct 19, 1995; cuid6016; 310724 (Box 67, Cassette 136)
    - Celebrating Women's Month, Apr 12, 1996; cuid6017; 310725 (Box 67, Cassette 137)
    - [Unidentified Program], May 17, 1996; cuid6018; 310726 (Box 67, Cassette 138)
    - Domestic Violence, Jun 7, 1996; cuid6019; 310727 (Box 67, Cassette 139)
    - Economics at DC 37, Oct 23, 1996; cuid6020; 310728 (Box 67, Cassette 140)
    - Black History: Tuskegee Airmen, Feb 5, 1997; cuid6021; 310729 (Box 67, Cassette 141)
    - Black History: Tuskegee Airmen [DAT Cassette], Feb 5, 1997; cuid6022; 310730 (Box 67, Cassette 142)
    - [Unidentified Interview DAT Cassette], Sep 8, 1997; cuid6023; 310731 (Box 67, Cassette 143)
    - Hidden Disabilities Interview, Sep 18, 1997; cuid6024; 310732 (Box 67, Cassette 144)
    - AFL-CIO Convention, Sep 31, 1997; cuid6025; 310733 (Box 67, Cassette 145)
    - Black History Celebration, Feb 27, 1998; cuid6026; 310734 (Box 67, Cassette 146-147)
  - Subseries VIII:B: Other Radio Shows Audio Cassettes, 1979-1997., 310723
    - "Building Bridges": Gay and Lesbian Issues, Undated; cuid6027; 310735 (Box 67, Cassette 148)
    - "Building Bridges": Local 1930 Rally, Undated; cuid6028; 310736 (Box 67, Cassette 149)
    - "Public Employee": Gus Tyler and Victor Gotbaum, Undated; cuid6029; 310737 (Box 67, Cassette 150)
    - "Political Action" (DC 37), Jun 20, 1979; cuid6030; 310738 (Box 67, Cassette 151)
    - "Good Times, Bad Times": Local 372, 1982; cuid6031; 310739 (Box 67, Cassette 152)
    - "Newsbeat": Are Unions in Trouble? (with Victor Gotbaum), 1984; cuid6032; 310740 (Box 67, Cassette 153)
    - "Building Bridges": Teamsters Local 810 Strikers, Jun 4, 1987; cuid6033; 310741 (Box 67, Cassette 154)
    - "English Language Skills" (DC 37 Educational Fund), Feb 6, 1991; cuid6034; 310742 (Box 67, Cassette 155)
    - "Building Bridges": Morris Dees (Southern Poverty Law Center), Gathering Storm: America's Militia Threat, May 13, 1996; cuid6035; 310743 (Box 67, Cassette 156)
    - Educational Fund and Women's Council Program, Mar 31, 1997; cuid6036; 310744 (Box 67, Cassette 157)
    - HRA Commissioner/Jason Turner, Jun 30, 1998; cuid6037; 311487 (Box 67, Cassette 248)
    - Interview with Eric Lars Nelson of Newsday, Oct 5, 1998; cuid6038; 311488 (Box 67, Cassette 249)
    - Tom Defrank, Oct 8, 1998; cuid6039; 311489 (Box 67, Cassette 250)
    - Nita Lowey, Oct 8, 1998; cuid6040; 311490 (Box 67, Cassette 251)
    - Foster Care, Oct 21, 1998; cuid6041; 311491 (Box 67, Cassette 252)
    - Newsday/Marie Coco, Oct 30, 1998; cuid6042; 311492 (Box 67, Cassette 253)
    - Dennis Duggan/Lanny Sanjek, Nov 16, 1998; cuid6043; 311493 (Box 67, Cassette 254)
  - Subseries VIII:C: Radio Spots Audio Cassettes, 1979-1987., 310745
    - City Council Committee on Aging Hearings, Report, Undated; cuid6044; 310746 (Box 67, Cassette 158)
    - Meeting Union Members, Mar 1, 1979; cuid6045; 310747 (Box 67, Cassette 159)
    - City Workers Advise Public About City Services (6 Spots), May 17, 1984; cuid6046; 310748 (Box 67, Cassette 160)
    - City Workers Advise Public About City Services (11 Spots), Jun 5, 1984; cuid6047; 310749 (Box 67, Cassette 161)
    - Hall, Sonny and Victor Gotbaum on MTA Contract Negotiations, 1986; cuid6048; 310750 (Box 67, Cassette 162)
    - Employees for Improved Transit (3 Spots), 1986; cuid6049; 310751 (Box 67, Cassette 163)
    - DC 37 Contract Negotiations (4 Spots), 1987; cuid6050; 310752 (Box 67, Cassette 164-167)
  - Subseries VIII:D: Interviews and Speeches Audio Cassettes, 1979-1999., 310753
    - Bernstein, Rachel and Gail Malmgreen Interview on Debra Bernhardt, Mar 2001; cuid6051; 338782 (Box 67, Cassette 167a)
    - Castillo, Luisa Amelia, Marian Porro, and Lynn Taylor Interview, Undated; cuid6052; 310844 (Box 67, Cassette 168)
    - Claxton, Anna (Local 372) Speech, Jul 25, 1979; cuid6053; 310845 (Box 67, Cassette 169)
    - Clinton, Bill Speech to Trade Unionists, Undated; cuid6054; 310846 (Box 67, Cassette 170)
    - Gotbaum, Victor Speech on Mayor John Lindsay, Undated; cuid6055; 310847 (Box 67, Cassette 171)
    - Gotbaum, Victor Speech to DC 37 Delegates, Jan 29, 1987; cuid6056; 310848 (Box 67, Cassette 172)
    - Hill, Stanley and Ralph Neas Interview, Jan 19, 1987; cuid6057; 310849 (Box 67, Cassette 173)
    - Hill, Stanley Interview on Contract Negotiations, Oct 18, 1990; cuid6058; 310850 (Box 67, Cassette 174)
    - Hill, Stanley Speech: "Just Like You", Undated; cuid6059; 310851 (Box 67, Cassette 175)
    - Hill, Stanley Speech at Local 372 Black History Month Celebration, Feb 20, 1998; cuid6060; 310852 (Box 67, Cassette 176)
    - Howard, Al Interview on Corruption in City Government, Undated; cuid6061; 310853 (Box 67, Cassette 177)
    - Hughes, Charles and Victor Gotbaum Speeches to Local 372, Mar 8, 1982; cuid6062; 310854 (Box 67, Cassette 178)
    - Jackson, Jesse Speech at UAW Rally, Feb 23, 1988; cuid6063; 310855 (Box 67, Cassette 179)
    - Kerstein, Goodie and Catherine Bruno Interview (Local 372), Jul 19, 1979; cuid6064; 310856 (Box 67, Cassette 180)
    - Labor Day Parades Interviews, Undated; cuid6065; 310857 (Box 67, Cassette 181)
    - Library Guild Leaders Interviews at Rally (Local 1930), Oct 21, 1999; cuid6066; 310858 (Box 67, Cassette 182)
    - Mackey, [Nathaniel?] Interview on "Black Language", Undated; cuid6067; 310859 (Box 67, Cassette 183)
    - Mandela, Nelson Speech at Unknown AFSCME Conference, Undated; cuid6068; 310860 (Box 67, Cassette 184)
    - Richards, Ann Speech, San Diego, Undated; cuid6069; 310861 (Box 67, Cassette 185)
    - Roberts, Lillian Speech at Rally (introduction by James Butler), Undated; cuid6070; 310862 (Box 67, Cassette 186)
    - Unidentified Participants Interview on UFT Contract, Undated; cuid6071; 310863 (Box 67, Cassette 187)
    - Unidentified Participants Interview on Unidentified Subject, Undated; cuid6072; 310864 (Box 67, Cassette 188)
    - Wildavsky, Aaron Interview (author of Speaking Truth to Power), Mar 19, 1981; cuid6073; 310865 (Box 67, Cassette 189)
  - Subseries VIII:E: Conferences and Conventions Audio Cassettes, 1983-1997., 310866
    - AFL-CIO Organizing Conference, Apr 29, 1997; cuid6074; 310867 (Box 67, Cassette 190)
    - AFSCME Conference: "Welfare Reform for Work and Dignity" (tape 1 of 2), Dec 3, 1996; cuid6075; 310868 (Box 67, Cassette 191)
    - AFSCME Conference: "Welfare Reform for Work and Dignity" (tape 2 of 2), Dec 3, 1996; cuid6076; 310869 (Box 67, Cassette 192)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 1 of 3), 1992; cuid6077; 310870 (Box 67, Cassette 193)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 2 of 3), 1992; cuid6078; 310871 (Box 67, Cassette 194)
    - AFSCME 30th Annual International Convention, Las Vegas (tape 3 of 3), 1992; cuid6079; 310872 (Box 67, Cassette 195)
    - AFSCME Convention Speech by Bill Lucy, 1996; cuid6080; 310873 (Box 67, Cassette 196)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation", 1985; cuid6081; 310874 (Box 67, Cassette 197)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation" Workshop, "New Forms and Structures", 1985; cuid6082; 310875 (Box 67, Cassette 198)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation" Workshop on Public Opinion and Public Relations (tape 1 of 2), 1985; cuid6083; 310876 (Box 67, Cassette 199)
    - DC 37 Conference: "Changing Situation" Workshop on Public Opinion and Public Relations (tape 2 of 2), 1985; cuid6084; 310877 (Box 67, Cassette 200)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Introduction [DAT Cassette], Jun 22, 1991; cuid6085; 310878 (Box 67, Cassette 201)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Gerald McEntee [DAT Cassette], Jun 22, 1991; cuid6086; 310879 (Box 67, Cassette 202)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Closing Speech, Jul 14, 1987; cuid6087; 310880 (Box 67, Cassette 203)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Speech, Jul 14, 1987; cuid6088; 310881 (Box 67, Cassette 204)
    - DC 37 Educational Conference: Stanley Hill Speech [DAT Cassette], 1995; cuid6089; 310882 (Box 67, Cassette 205)
    - DC 37 Professional Division Conference: Roundtable Discussion (tape 1 of 2), 1985; cuid6090; 310883 (Box 67, Cassette 206)
    - DC 37 Professional Division Conference: Roundtable Discussion (tape 2 of 2), 1985; cuid6091; 310884 (Box 67, Cassette 207)
    - Hospitals Conference (tape 1 of 2), May 2, 1987; cuid6092; 310885 (Box 67, Cassette 208)
    - Hospitals Conference (tape 2 of 2), May 2, 1987; cuid6093; 310886 (Box 67, Cassette 209)
    - Lesbian and Gay East Coast Conference (tape 1 of 2), Undated; cuid6094; 310887 (Box 67, Cassette 210)
    - Lesbian and Gay East Coast Conference (tape 2 of 2), Undated; cuid6095; 310888 (Box 67, Cassette 211)
    - Local 436 Conference: "Mainstreaming Handicapped", 1983; cuid6096; 310889 (Box 67, Cassette 212)
    - Local 436 Conference: "Mainstreaming Handicapped" Speech by Annie [?], 1983; cuid6097; 310890 (Box 67, Cassette 213)
    - Unknown Conference: Speech by Bill Lucy, Undated; cuid6098; 310891 (Box 67, Cassette 214)
  - Subseries VIII:F: Other Events Audio Cassettes, 1987-1997., 310892
    - AFL-CIO Officers Election Forum (tape 1 of 2), May 22, 1996; cuid6099; 310893 (Box 67, Cassette 215)
    - AFL-CIO Officers Election Forum (tape 2 of 2), May 22, 1996; cuid6100; 310894 (Box 67, Cassette 216)
    - AFL-CIO "Union Summer" Press Conference, May 1, 1996; cuid6101; 310895 (Box 67, Cassette 217)
    - Clinton, Bill Health Care Plan Press Conference, Undated; cuid6102; 310896 (Box 68, Cassette 218)
    - Collective Bargaining Meeting, Jan 5, 1987; cuid6103; 310897 (Box 68, Cassette 219)
    - Contract Agreement Press Conference, Oct 24, 1994; cuid6104; 310898 (Box 68, Cassette 220)
    - Contract Agreement Press Conference, City Hall, Undated; cuid6105; 310899 (Box 68, Cassette 221)
    - Cornell University Labor Scholars Panel Discussion, Undated; cuid6106; 310900 (Box 68, Cassette 222)
    - DC 37 Fashion Show, Undated; cuid6107; 310901 (Box 68, Cassette 223)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 1 of 3), Jul 13, 1987; cuid6108; 310902 (Box 68, Cassette 224)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 2 of 3), Jul 13, 1987; cuid6109; 310903 (Box 68, Cassette 225)
    - DC 37 General Session (tape 3 of 3), Jul 13, 1987; cuid6110; 310904 (Box 68, Cassette 226)
    - DC 37 Hispanic Heritage Month Celebration (tape 1 of 2), Undated; cuid6111; 310905 (Box 68, Cassette 227)
    - DC 37 Hispanic Heritage Month Celebration (tape 2 of 2), Undated; cuid6112; 310906 (Box 68, Cassette 228)
    - DC 37 Nominating Meeting, Jan 27, 1987; cuid6113; 310907 (Box 68, Cassette 229)
    - DC 37 Unidentified Event [DAT Cassette], Undated; cuid6114; 310908 (Box 68, Cassette 230)
    - DC 37 Women's Committee Awards Dinner (tape 1 of 2), Mar 20, 1997; cuid6115; 310909 (Box 68, Cassette 231)
    - DC 37 Women's Committee Awards Dinner, Mar 20, 1997; cuid6116; 310910 (Box 68, Cassette 232)
    - Financial Crisis Panel Discussion, Nov 26, 1991; cuid6117; 310911 (Box 68, Cassette 233)
    - Gay Pride Authors [Blank?], Jul 9, 1996; cuid6118; 310912 (Box 68, Cassette 234)
    - International Change, Globalization, and the European Union Forum, Feb 10, 1996; cuid6119; 310913 (Box 68, Cassette 235)
    - Labor and the Community Forum, Mar 31, [?]; cuid6120; 310914 (Box 68, Cassette 236)
    - Labor and the Community Forum [DAT Cassette], Mar 31, [?]; cuid6121; 310915 (Box 68, Cassette 237)
    - Local 420 Rally at First Baptist Church, Dec 18, 1996; cuid6122; 310916 (Box 68, Cassette 238)
    - McEntee, Gerald W., undated; cuid6123; 593091 (Box 68, Cassette 248)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 1 of 3), Mar 1, 1994; cuid6124; 310917 (Box 68, Cassette 239)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 2 of 3), Mar 1, 1994; cuid6125; 310918 (Box 68, Cassette 240)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 3 of 3), Mar 1, 1994; cuid6126; 310919 (Box 68, Cassette 241)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 1 of 2) [beginning inaudible], Jan 18, 1995; cuid6127; 310920 (Box 68, Cassette 242)
    - Privatization Panel Discussion (tape 2 of 2), Jan 18, 1995; cuid6128; 310921 (Box 68, Cassette 243)
    - Rifkin, Bernie Dedication, Dec 11, 1995; cuid6129; 310922 (Box 68, Cassette 244)
    - Social Security Advisory Committee Report Press Conference, Jan 6, 1997; cuid6130; 310923 (Box 68, Cassette 245)
    - Tuberculosis Panel Discussion, Undated; cuid6131; 310924 (Box 68, Cassette 246)
    - Unidentified Event, Undated; cuid6132; 310925 (Box 68, Cassette 247)
- Series IX: Ken Nash Collection - 2015 Donation, 1993-2014; 2015.062; 591634
  - District Council 37 Radio Broadcasts, 1993-2003; 1998-2003; cuid6133; 591635 (Box 70)
  - Award Dinner and Banquet Programs, 2012, 2014; cuid6134; 591636 (Box 71)
  - 65th Anniversary Commemorative History Book, 2009; cuid6135; 591637 (Box 71)
  - Labor Magazines, 2014; cuid6136; 591638 (Box 71)
- Series X: Audio Reels - Other, 1965; 310567
  - 40 Audio Reels (appear to be radio spots--some are in Spanish), 1965, undated; cuid6137; 311041 (Box 69)
- Series XI: Archived Website, Sep 24, 2007-ongoing; cuid6138; 544995
  District Council 37 (DC 37) is a local union of the American Federation of State, County, and Municipal Employees (AFSCME) which represents New York City public employees and employees in the healthcare industry. DC 37 was founded in 1944. The website contains information on locals, contracts and agreements, news listings, press releases, their newsletter, Public Employee Press, their political action campaign, and member benefits and services.
  Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
  Due to technical or privacy issues, archived websites may not be exact copies of the original website at the time of the web crawl. Certain file types will not be captured dependent on how they are embedded in the site. Other parts of websites that the crawler has difficulty capturing includes Javascript, streaming content, database-driven content, and highly interactive content. Full-Text searches of archived websites are available at https://archive-it.org/organizations/567.
- Series XII: Films and videos, 1972-1999
  - Dignity of Work Series (Films, Inc.), "Clerical Workers", 1972-10-10; cuid6139 (Film wag.265_cuid6139, Box Digitized Access Files, File wag.265_cuid6139)
  - Dignity of Work Series (Films, Inc.), "Marketing Inspector", 1972-10-06; cuid6140 (Film wag.265_cuid6140, Box Digitized Access Files, File wag.265_cuid6140)
  - Dignity of Work Series (Films, Inc.), "Zoo Keeper", 1972-12-06; cuid6141 (Film tamwag_wag.265_cuid6141, Box Digitized Access Files, File wag.265_cuid6141)
  - Videos: "Keep the Doors Open," "In the Name of Corporate Greed," "Postal Workers Fight Privatization", 1998-1999; cuid6142 (Box Shared Tamiment 012)
  - Video: "Jason Turner," Up Close New York One, 1998-07-23; cuid6143 (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
  - Video: "America's Victory: The 1997 UPS Strike", undated; cuid6144 (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
  - Video: 1. Joe DeCanio, L. 376, 2. 60 Minutes-Mark Rosenthal, L. 983, undated; cuid6145 (Box Shared Tamiment 013)
  - Unprocessed Videos (Box 72)